From my point of view, he's great at variety, but he's also a great singer.
I'm a great variety singer, and I've been doing music since I was an idol.
I've also been acting since I was an idol.
I'm often asked which is what I really want to do. Like, "Which is what you really want to do?
I get asked that a lot. Yes, I get asked that a lot.
Of course music is important to me, and I want to do it,
But I don't have to choose everything, do I? I'm just doing it in a casual way,
How much do you think about that?
If I had to choose whether I want to do it or not, I would say I want to do it all. If I say I want to do anything, it might sound rude to all the jobs I do, so I try my best not to say that, but I started out in acting, but before that I was in bands all the time, even when I was a student.
I don't usually watch a lot of movies or practice acting.
Oh, I see.
Not at all.
I started playing music when I was in junior high school, and I started reading audition forms for the entertainment industry, you know?
I would send in a barrage of audition magazines.
I would go to Tokyo by myself and go to the office and do the "kon-kon-kon.
Send it out like this.
And they said, "Please don't do that.
I had my own office.
I had my first office when I was in high school.
They just said, "Okay," and that was it, but at that time
But at that time, you were doing it right.
You did it.
I'm going to invite a guest who wants to talk now and talk about it.
How did you get involved with Variety?
Variety is because I know about variety.
Because I know about variety
Because they know about variety
I'm going to be in this show because of the same reason I was in a show called "Billy Idol," but I've already held it.
Well, I had been a big promoter of idol events and stuff like that, and I was doing mc and stuff like that, and I was talking a lot, and I guess she saw that, and she said it was a night when women get mad at women.
And then there was an audition, and they were looking for new girls.
I think there were about 50 to 100 people? They had an audition.
And I went to it. I came to Biri Idol.
I went in there and I said bad things about them.
I talked a lot, and I talked a lot about other people,
And then I passed the audition and got out, so that's new again.
I did music and acting,
I thought I was going to be in a music group like Puffy for a long time, but then variety came along.
And then, by chance, Billy Idol ran out of money and was told that they were breaking up.
Oh, it's the money.
Yeah, well, I guess it didn't work out.
So it kind of ends.
But it's a good thing it's over, because Corona's here.
Oh, I see.
If Corona had come in, it probably would have been a sadder end.
I don't think we would have been able to do any gigs.
Is that when you left?
I left before Corona, too. Right around that time.
I don't want to say that I've done everything I can, but even in the idol world, it would be nice if I could make it into something like the "anything era".
It would be nice if we could make it into something like the "what-if" era.
That's exactly what I did with V-S.
I was able to make Al.
Yeah, yeah.
So I think I've already made a break.
I've come to the end of my rope.
I had no choice but to quit.
I'd already lost my mind.
Yeah, yeah.
I quit.
I quit music, variety, acting...
I quit because I didn't want to do anything else.
You mean you're thinking of going back to a normal life?
Yes, I'm going to go back to a reclusive life.
I don't really have a choice, I'm just doing whatever comes my way.
But my original reason for doing this is because I'm an actor, and I'm glad that I'm doing so many dramas now.
Anochan, did you start working on Vassar's drama after Corona?
That was before Corona.
When I was an idol for the first time.
During "Iramemon"?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, really?
I only remember that acting is very difficult.
You had to do the same thing over and over again?
Yes, it was.
I think it was so hard, but it was over in such a short period of time.
When I look at my parents.
I don't even know how to play the role of an ordinary office worker, but they worked so hard.She played the role of a normal person, like an ordinary female office worker.
The one with Mr. Wassan, he played a manicurist or something, a regular guy, right?
Yes, he was a normal guy.
Unexpectedly, yes.
That was difficult. Was it difficult? He was trying really hard.
I blink a lot, so who's going to tell me not to blink?
I was asked to be a regular nail artist because I was becoming a ram, and it was such a small role, but it was tough.
But I was looking at it, and I was thinking that if they really wanted me to play a normal person, the director would probably have drawn me as that normal person.
That was great.
The result was a slightly different nail style.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was the first role where I didn't die.
Before that, I'd played all deaths.
I played ghosts and dead people.
You're right, I did die.
Yes, I was dead.
Ano, you have your own name, Ano, and you have another band, right? You have different songs and different things, but you're still the same person. So, even if Ano performs as a solo artist, she might have a band, for example.
The result is the same. The nature is the same.
What's the difference as a vocalist between Ano and with a band?
I don't know, I don't know.
The solo one, really, yeah.
I wonder if there is a God.
I don't know if there is a God or not.
I don't know if there is a God or not, but I don't think there is anyway.
It's the same with my private life.
I've had many experiences that made me think that God doesn't exist.
And when that happens, I think to myself, "Why don't I just become God?
That's what I'm trying to do.
I feel like no one is watching.
I'm trying to wrap everything up, and when I'm in the band, I feel like everything is melting.
I want to wrap it all up around me.
No substance?
It's melting and dissolving.
It's all dripping.
It's a place where it all drips and explodes as an emotion.
Wow.
I know, it's hard, but that's what it feels like to be in a place where you can just explode as a band.
I know, it's hard, but that's what it feels like.
You know, your solo stuff...
It's so easy to hold it up as an icon.
I think she's looking at it from the outside.
I feel like you're leaving it at that.
But with the band...
Melted into the space
There are eyes floating in the space
It's like there's an eye floating in the air in space.
It's like...
It's like a different perspective.
So maybe you're part of it.
might be a part of it.
Or maybe the band is part of it.
Or maybe they're all mixed up.
Or maybe there's nothing.
So it's not that it's true or false, it's just that there is no boundary between the skin and the country, but it feels like a mess.
I don't even know if I was there or not as a solo artist. I don't even know if I was there or not. I don't even know if I was there or not.
It's like being in a dream.
That's right.
You're in it, aren't you?
Yes, it is.
I was riding that thing like Eva,
And when I got off, I wondered if it was me.
But you remember moving it.
Yes. It's strange. I wonder if my thoughts are mixed up or not.
I think there are mixed thoughts and unmixed memories.
I don't think only one person is the engine of an artist anon.
A lot of things come with it.
Good things and bad things.
That's why they're probably iconic.
In fact, since the group, I've been thinking about that gal, that girl.
You know what I mean? She is an icon.
There are a lot of them. That's the kind of fan you are.
That's right. That's why there's a gap that was created on its own, and that's how she actually is.
Ever since she was an idol.
Each of us has our own image of her,
If you deviate from that image, it is seen as an act of betrayal.
But, seeing that, new fans come to see her, right?
That's right.
It's amazing that she can honestly say everything like this, and it's like she's new, and even though she joined the group because she was really good at it, she's not able to grow as a performer on TV.
He's so kind, but that's not what I'm talking about.
There's a cut, isn't there? We don't talk about this kind of thing very often.
I have a lot of questions I need to ask you.I have a lot of questions I need to ask you.
Really? Really?
Do you have any time off?
No, I don't.
When I'm off, I go to the arcade by myself.
Arcade? What do you do?
I play crane games.
You like crane games? Are you good at it?
I'm not good at it, but I'll play until I get it. Do you like crane games? Are you good at it?
I'm not good at it, but I just play until I get it.
But I like it a lot.
I'm not good at it, but I'm the type of person who plays all the time.
Idol?
But I've been doing a lot of different things.
Recently, there's a fish keychain called "Fish Ghost.
I only do the ones with fish.
I only do the ones that have me.
I only want the ones that have them.
But I don't know much.
I read a lot of Jump manga.
I've read a lot of Jump manga, like Jutsu Kakudo, or Chainsaw Man, for that matter.
There are a lot of them.
I thought it would be better for me to read them, so I did.
That's great!
I thought you seemed to like the jump stuff of unexpected people.
Don't you meet a lot of people at all? Not at the moment.
I'm not afraid to say that I choose the people I meet.
I'm really selective.
I guess you're right.
It's...
It's stressful.
I don't want to talk to people I don't like.
I'll say it with someone I feel comfortable with.
Do you ever ask people out on your own?
No, I don't think so.
No? Even if he's easy?
I like to be alone as much as possible.
That's pretty similar.
I like to be alone too.
That's why I go to the arcade alone.
I go to karaoke alone.
I go to the arcade by myself, and I go to karaoke by myself, too!
Both alone.
It's hard to keep up with the schedule.
Yes, I understand.
I'm simply too busy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't have time.
It's the only place to be.
Yeah, I know.
I'm on that channel, but, you know, maybe next time we can do the crane game episode.
Oh, sure, let's do it!
Yes, yes! Teach me mah-jongg.
I don't know enough to teach you.
Oh, really?
Well, I can.
Yeah, I can.
I don't know where to start.
Oh, like this.
You can't do the math on a scale of one to ten, can you? Calculating scores.
I always leave all the scoring to others.
Oh, leave it to others.
It's best to leave it to others.
Oh, that's right, Aro-chan, that's what I'm talking about. Normally, I leave it to others. It's best to leave it to others. That's right.
That's what I envy about you, Ano.
That's what I envy about you, Ano,
For example.
Just the fact that you can open the lid of a jam by yourself makes me feel really good.
I'm sure there must be someone around you who would ask you to open it. There must be someone around you.
There are so many of them.
Right?
That's what I don't like.
Over-involvement?
I feel like I'm being licked.
No, I can open that.
I can't help it. I'm just me.
Amano Jack Corner.
Yeah, I'm Jack Amano.
So there's that.
Yes, I'm Jack Amelo, so there's that.
Who's the easiest MC to work with? I don't know.
But I'm sure he's a nice guy.But I think he's a kind man.
If I were to give out business cards like this.
Mr. Ueda of Cream Stew...
I thought it would be easy.
You thought so, didn't you?
He asked me to be kind on and on, and he definitely handled it.
Mr. Ueda was the first one to come out,
Because it was Mr. Ueda, there is a possibility that it would have worked out well.
And then, of course, there was Downtown,
I think it's great.
It would be rude to say that both of them are easy to work with,
But you are scary, aren't you? He is a legend.
He has an aura.
Yes, you can tell he's the real deal.
He's cool.
But isn't he very kind?
He's so kind.
He listens to what you have to say, and even when you're not down, he blows you out of the water,
Even the fans of El Melmo,
I've seen Mana-chan on variety shows like this, going at it with Mr. Mitsuhachi,
I'm sure there are a lot of people who say it's a strange feeling to see Mana-chan engaging in a bar fight with Mr. Mitsuhachi on variety TV.
They said they couldn't imagine a future in which they would be involved with Downtown.
I couldn't imagine it," some of them say.
They will say that.
And then there's Yamasato-san, whose true feelings might make me angry if I don't say something.
Hahahahaha!
No, it's too loud.
He says, "You didn't mention my name.
That's what they say.
I saw that.
I don't like it.
They didn't mention my name.
Hahahahaha!
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you, they'll say it on junk. They'll say it on junk.
They will say so.
I don't know if Yamasato-san is kind or not,
He always responds to my answers with a burst of laughter,
He always responds, and he always makes it interesting, so I think he is kind.
Mr. Yamasato, you know, he has a bad temperament.
That's what I don't like about him, he really scares me.
But I'm glad that there are people who are willing to put that kind of thing out there and still do mc.
It gives me hope.
What do you want to do from now on? What do you want to do in the future?
What do you want to do now that you're weak in this area? Or something like that.
And what kind of movies you want to be in.
Oh, I see.
I have only been performing on stage for a short time, so I think I need to rapidly learn and work on dramas and movies, which are completely different.
I think music and acting are the two things you can do for the longest time, because you can only produce what you can produce at that age.
Aging is not a stumbling block.
If you were an idol, getting older would probably be a negative thing.
But with acting and music, the more you age, the more you can bring out different things.
I want to do music, but I don't think music will ever be commercially viable.
I don't think I'll ever be able to perform at the Tokyo Dome by myself.
But there is a possibility that I could be in a film festival, for example,
I think life is more enjoyable if you take the one with the highest probability.
Anchan's current projects
Ano, the band, and
And there's another talent, Ano, with hiragana.
Well, I guess music.
The center of gravity is...
And I think that's what TV is all about.
There's always a stumbling block.
You're going to have a hard time.
I don't know how I'll feel at that time.
If I felt like quitting then, I would have quit right away.
So you're going to withdraw?
Yeah, and then you'll make music, won't you?
Music? You're not interested in making music?
Composing?
I wasn't interested in composing at first.
But as I got into it, I thought it would be fun.
I never thought about offering it to other people.
But I thought it would be nice to have a future in it, so I wrote lyrics.
Yes, yes...
Is that all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
The end.
But I don't talk this slow.But I never talk this slow.
How was it? Was it hard? Are you okay?
I'm glad you were so easy to talk to.
I'm glad you were easy to talk to. I thought he had a very realistic way of dreaming.
Realistic.
He's a real man of the streets.
He's got his feet in the blood.
I'm glad I got to know that.
Please subscribe to our amateur channel!